[{"answer": "People. Can I", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Are you Tiny my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "That's true... Only my boss on the paper can't see it that way", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Whose business is it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He's the head man", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He's in a position to know nothin'. And to say nothin'", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He's in a position to know nothin'. And to say nothin'", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " He uses my head", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Yeah, I apologized to my friend", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, I gave 'em back", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Did you give him his handbills back", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Give him back his flag and his bag and...  give this man his camera", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Orange pop! All right, Sugar Boy. Bring him some orange pop", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Did you hear that, boys? The ", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You do very well at it. I read your articles about this fellow... my friend. Very convincing... Too convincing for my tastes", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A lot of people are fools. Articles like that shouldn't be permitted. They only tend to incite people", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Honest man? This state is full of these lo", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes, don't you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Are you afraid I can't make a living", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What is it you want me to be", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh, no, my friend, it isn't that. I don't care about the money. It... it's just that I... I want you to be something", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't know. It's just that I want you to be... to do... something important", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "...Measure of the damages is caused by..", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "A breach..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "A breach..", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Of an agreement..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Of an agreement..", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "To sell...  Oh, two years of this", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Which is", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Smart people", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Enough? He didn't even get anything out of it. Oh, they'd have paid you to take a rap like that, but they didn't have to pay a sap like you. Oh, no, you were so full of yourself and hot air, all you wanted was a chance to stand up on your hind legs and make a speec", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " He wants to know if it's true", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Is it true", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Is it true", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Yeah, I quieted him down", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " You're smart. 'Cause before I'm through with that mob they're not going to have enough money left to pay the boy that cleans the spittoons", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I feel fine, fine. You see, my friend, I learned something", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " Come on, come on, come on, come on. Are these the boys", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "How many do you think we can get", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You tell me, Mr. my friend", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, I didn't... There's another question I'd like to ask you. You say there's only bad to start with and the good must come with the bad. Who's to determine what's good and what's bad?... You", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "It's a fact, a blasphemous fact", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I understand that", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I got that", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "It's too true", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " It took you a long time to make up your mind, Judge. A long time. What made you take such a long time", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "And now you are", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Do you think I like sneaking around corners any more than you do? But right now, with the that place business and with your uncle quitting... If I got a divorce..", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "No. No, we won't stop seeing each other, will we", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " Because I believe what you tell me", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "my friend, I want to ask you a question. Was the Judge ever broke? Really broke", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I don't want to know, but I've got to", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I don't want to know, but I've got to", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Did who tell me", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "What other things", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Yes, me too", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "my friend knows everything", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "my friend's boy is worried about my friend's boy", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Go on upstairs, my friend. I have some business I want to talk over with Mr. my friend", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Now... now, don't get excited.  Get me another drink, Sugar", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Accidents? Your boy was drunk", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Whose police and whose report? I say the boy was drunk. And I know it", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I don't care what the police report says. I was driving and I was drunk. It's all my fault.  Anything you want to do to me, you can do. Whatever you want me to do, I'll do", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I don't want you to take care of anything", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "I didn't say", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Trucking business", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Oh, you know what I'm talking about", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "About my friend and me", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "my friend... my friend, why did you do it", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You mean he wasn't like me", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "He wasn't like anybody I ever knew before", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "He wasn't like anybody I ever knew before. I love him, I guess. I guess that's the reason", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "You don't know him. You've known him all these years and you don't really know him at all", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "To do some good for the people of the state", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Oh, there are lots of ways to get votes", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "How many theaters will this play in", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Hear that, my friend. All over the country", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "They're lined up against you solid. They had a meeting", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Me? What would I be doing there", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "All right, give him a break. But if you got the facts, you got the facts. The truth is sufficient... just like it says in the Bible", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "All right, boy... I'll trust you. Where are you going", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "We've got a lot to do. It's getting late, my friend. Let's get back to town", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Aw, you don't mean that, boy", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "It's all right, doc. Just here to discuss some politics with the Judge", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Stop it", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "I know. I was here", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "Tell him what", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "About you and my friend", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "For who? Your brother, or my friend", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "Who's through with who", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "Who's through with who", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "Better for who? Him", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "I don't know. Leave me alone", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "I don't care", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "No, that's too easy", "docId": "All-the-King_s-Men.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 102}]